(Howard:)Sorry. Do you have a...
sense of where we are?
(Mr Rostenkowski:)Yeah. I think that's the den.
(Howard:)Oh. Okay, so we must be
under the dining room.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)Uh-huh. Yep.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)You know, I know you
don't want to hear this,
(Mr Rostenkowski:)but it wouldn't take that
much work to turn that den
(Mr Rostenkowski:)into a nursery.
(Howard:)Why wouldn't I want to hear it?
'Cause Bernie said
you didn't want kids.
(Howard:)That's not true at all.
I-I wish
(Howard:)she'd get pregnant, believe me.
(Howard:)I'm climbing on top of her
every chance I get.
(sighs)
(Howard:)In a... loving
and respectful manner.
(Raj:)Oh.
(clears throat softly)
(Howard:)The point is,
(Howard:)I really do want kids.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)Huh.
(Howard:)I don't know why
she's lying to you.
WOLOWITZ: She's the one
who doesn't want kids.
(Howard:)In fact, every time I
bring up the subject...
Earthquake!
(Bernadette's feet
stomping rapidly)
(Penny:)Oh, my God,
we're gonna die!
Earthquake!
Aftershock...!